INNA HORBOVTSOVA



603 727 2313

iwali2607.wixsite.com/innahportfolio

innahorbovtsova@gmail.com

Graphic Designer

PROFILE

Creative and organized student enrolled in Digital Media Communications Associate Degree seeking a one-year internship or a one-year full-time job, preferably paid. Aiming to develop skills in graphic design, communication, software, marketing, print knowledge, editorial layout, typography, client relations and teamwork while contributing to an organization.

SKILLS

- Adobe Creative Suite:
- Adobe Photoshop (Proficient)
- Adobe Illustrator (Proficient)
- -Adobe InDesign (Proficient)
- Adobe Lightroom (Moderate)
- -Adobe After Effects (In Progress)
- Language skills:
- English (Fluent)
- Ukrainian (Fluent)
- Russian (Fluent)

HONORS

- Phita Keppa Honor Society (2019 - present)
- President's list (2019)

Volunteer work:

- Project GRAD
- Student mentor
- Exeter High School
- Gave seminars on history and culture of Ukraine
- Strawberry Banke Museum
- Helped set up festivals

EDUCATION

Anticipated May 2020

Associate Degree in Digital Media Communications Great Bay Community College (3.95 GPA)

2011-2015

Bachelor's Degree in Foreign Language and Literature National Academy of State Border Guard Service of Ukraine named after Bohdan Khmelnitskyi

EXPERIENCE

• Peer Tutor and Lab Assistant at the Center of Academic Planning and Support of GBCC

June 2019-present time

- Led one-on-one appointments with students, tutored such subjects as Intro to Computers, Intro to Object Oriented Program, Introduction to Graphic Design, Introduction to Photoshop, College Composition, Nutrition.
- Undertook clerical responsibilities and resolved campus related inquiries from students. Frequently designed bulletin boards school-wide.
- President of GBCC International Club September 2019-present time
- -Fostered teamwork and collaboration by planning meetings and allocating responsibilities. Designed publicity and promotional materials, organized events and activities.
- Au Pair in America May 2016- May 2018
- Participated in exchange program that required living with a host family and taking care of their kids up to 45 hours per week.